I'm at the upper level here in Camden Market now and have an appointment going
to meet with Max from Fab London. Let's go!
Oh, hello! Welcome! Welcome to Fab London!
Thank you! So, thanks for having me.
You're welcome.
I have a few questions.
Okay.
How long are you operating Fab London already?
So, Fab London has been now six years.
Wow.
Yes.
In Camden?
Yes, all in Camden.
How would you describe the range of products you're offering here?
Eclectic, we offer everything from high-end fashion to toys to art to furniture, you name it, we've got a lot.
So you've got everyone covered who's looking for something exclusive and extravagant.
Correct, yes, and from lots of different designers and artists.
Okay, I tried on a dress from the personal collection of Marnie Scarlett and it comes
with a lot of accessories like this cute little bow, but I'll link it in the description text
so you can have a look at yourself.
I'm going to go outside
so you can have a better look at the dress.
If someone wants to go to their first fetish party,
what kind of outfit or item would you recommend?
Well, normally what happens is I have people coming to me and I take them by the hand as
it were and show them the ropes and that normally would, like for example what the mannequin
has on is quite a full on display and for first timers they are a bit more reluctant
to wear something like that so they ask me for basic items, you know, let's say high
high waist briefs, hot pants, halter neck, top, things like that, or for guys that tend
to go for like shorts or harness and things like that.
So you're also a stylist for people?
I am a fetish stylist, this is what I do, yeah.
So I'm not a designer, I've been a model and a stylist, but I don't design.
I just wear it beautifully.
What's your personal favourite piece here?
Oh, it will have to be, if you follow me, it will have to be this complete outfit made by my partner Marnie Scarlett,
who's a fetish designer and international artist and performer.
And this is just the bolero top.
So many ruffles. It must have taken ages.
So long to make.
It's like wearable art. That's how she describes it.
and it comes with a whole corset.
Yeah, absolutely.
And this is so heavy that you have corset boning
and poppers to keep it as a halo.
So what do you like about Camden?
Why did you set it up here?
Okay, so Camden had always had the draw
for anyone who was alternative.
So when I came to London in the 80s,
I had a foot and a half, that's half a meter, Mohawk, and I came here for punk.
So fetish wasn't, well it didn't exist, so it wasn't my thing, and that's what I came
for.
Camden was the place to be, together with a couple of places in the West End of London.
And we were here all the time.
In fact, on the lock where you can see the odd punk nowadays,
I used to be on the lock together,
but there was loads of us and it was amazing.
I have a photo.
I'm gonna ask you guys to add it on to this video.
You can check it out.
It's the only photo I have from that era.
You'll like it.
Nice, thank you.
You're very welcome.
Thank you.
you